<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>SVA Solutions - Misc</title><link href="https://josho88.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://josho88.github.io/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://josho88.github.io/</id><updated>2018-08-08T10:20:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Geospatial Risk Monitoring</title><link href="https://josho88.github.io/geospatial-risk-monitoring.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-08-08T10:20:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-08-08T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>SVA Solutions</name></author><id>tag:josho88.github.io,2018-08-08:/geospatial-risk-monitoring.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="geo-content"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;The web application below is an example of a solution we have developed to visually monitor insurance risks over time. Each data point on the map represents the level of risk at a postcode in the south west of England. The color and size of the location marker is determined …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="geo-content"&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;The web application below is an example of a solution we have developed to visually monitor insurance risks over time. Each data point on the map represents the level of risk at a postcode in the south west of England. The color and size of the location marker is determined by the size of the sum assured at that location - bigger risks have darker and bigger markers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;You can move the year input to see how the risk profile across this location changes over time. You can also zoom in to focus on a particular sub location. Clicking on a given marker will display a pop-up with information about the postcode, such as how much benefit is on risk there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;padding-bottom:25px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We can deploy tools like this to your websites or applications in just a single line of code.&lt;/strong&gt; If you're interested in a bespoke solution similar to this then &lt;a href="/pages/contact.html"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt; for a free consulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="holds-the-iframe"&gt;
&lt;iframe 0";="" ;"="" scrolling="no" src="https://josho88.shinyapps.io/geospatial" style="border: none; width: 100%; height: 600px; frameBorder="&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content></entry></feed>